With over 130 years of experience, we've chosen the
mission of partnering with our customers to make
easy decisions for a
better life and future every day.
Manulife's global journey began in
1887 in Canada, transcending borders to reach
continents, and arriving in Vietnam in 1999.
Manulife pursues the grand goal of
becoming a leading digital and customer-
centric company. Life is a
rich journey with important milestones
and hopes for a better future
every day, and we are always with you for
every important decision to make life
better every day, not
just in terms of prosperity but also health and well-
being. We support you and your
family with comprehensive financial solutions,
investment options, and
solutions for healthy living every day.
[Music]
We empathize and accompany you
on every journey to happiness and
prosperity for future generations. For over
20 years in Vietnam, Manulife
strives every day to make insurance
simpler, easier, and more accessible to
everyone.  Through
professional consultants, partners, and
online insurance platforms, Buylike proudly boasts a
team of dedicated financial advisors who are always
committed to their customers and is recognized
as a leading life insurance brand
in Vietnam. For a better life
every day, Manulife actively participates in many
community activities, accompanying
major sporting events across the country, promoting a
healthy lifestyle, and
always supporting Vietnam's victory. We are committed to helping Vietnam
overcome
difficulties caused by natural disasters and supporting
sustainable community development. This is the
journey we have chosen:
brighter new days with a more prosperous and open future.
Manulife is better every
day.